[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Best of Times, Jack Dundee and Reno Hightower sneak a peep at what TV event when they stop for dinner with their disgruntled wives?", "correct_answer": "Monday Night Football", "incorrect_answers": ["Sportscenter on ESPN", "Cotton Bowl", "Rose Bowl"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements about geckos is true?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Geckos have toe pads which help them climb smooth vertical surfaces.", "Geckos can make chirping sounds.", "Geckos feed on insects."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where do the lead singer and his wife live in one of the freecreditreport.com ads?", "correct_answer": "in the basement of her mom and dads", "incorrect_answers": ["at a traveling Renaissance Faire", "a pleasant suburb", "in the back of a fish n chips restaurant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What percentage of women do not wear the correct bra size?", "correct_answer": "50-75%", "incorrect_answers": ["20-40%", "30-40%", "10-15%"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Descent starring Shauna Macdonald was released in what year?", "correct_answer": "2005", "incorrect_answers": ["2008", "2001", "2003"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you roll two fair dice, what is the probability you will get a seven?", "correct_answer": "1/6", "incorrect_answers": ["1/36", "7/36", "7/6"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Love? Above all things I believe in love! Love is like oxygen! Love is a many splendored thing, love lifts us up where we belong, all you need is love! \n(2001)", "correct_answer": "Moulin Rouge", "incorrect_answers": ["Some Like It Hot", "Hope Floats", "Casablanca"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mias father dies at the end of the movie The Princess Diaries.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you were born in the year 1976, 1988 or 2000, what would your lunar sign be?", "correct_answer": "dragon", "incorrect_answers": ["horse", "snake", "rabbit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Without a Trace, a ful length animated film about a German ship sinking a ship of another nation, was released in 1918. In which country was the film made?", "correct_answer": "Argentina", "incorrect_answers": ["Germany", "The USA", "England"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Substance vital for treating what hereditary blood defect that occurs almost exclusively in males, has been produced by cloning?", "correct_answer": "Hemophilia", "incorrect_answers": ["Anemia", "Hemoglobinopaties", "Thalassemia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The cashew nutshell liquid, a by-product of cashew processing, contains anacardic acids, which are beneficial for the treatment of this medical problem.", "correct_answer": "Tooth abscesses", "incorrect_answers": ["Rashes", "Hair loss", "Varicose veins"]}]